We've been waiting so long.
Why is there still no sign of anyone?
I told you to stay at the residence.
But you insisted on coming with me.
It's been so long since I've seen A Lan.
I miss her terribly.
Now that she's finally returning to Luo Jing,
I naturally had to come welcome her.
Brother, you're no different.
Brother.
Support Admin Watch on
kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
I saw the portraits in your study.
The ones you painted in Jingzhou.
What were you doing in my study?
That's not important.
I never expected...
...you painted so many portraits of A Lan.
Brother.
You went to Jingzhou to treat the plague,
and agreed to serve in the court for His Majesty.
Was it all for A Lan?
Don't speak of this to anyone.
I know.
So when did you...
...start having feelings for A Lan?
Commander He.
Brother.
You lied to me.
I must have been mistaken.
What's going on between you and Commander He?
I heard from the maids at the residence.
While I was away from Luo Jing,
Commander He...
...kept sending you martial arts manuals for no reason.
What could possibly be between us?
He just offended me,
and sent a few lousy manuals as an apology.
A few?
What time is it already?
Why isn't A Lan back yet?
I'll go check over there.
Miss Meng.
What are you doing here?
I'm waiting for A Lan to return to the capital.
And you?
By His Majesty's order,
I had some business outside the city.
By the way,
once you finish practicing with these two manuals,
there will only be one left.
There are one hundred in total.
This final one...
...still has a little content left to complete.
I'll start writing it as soon as I return to my residence.
I'll definitely finish it tonight.
What's the rush?
I haven't even started on these two yet.
I have time tonight.
I might as well visit you at the Meng Residence.
What I mean is...
...tonight, I'll go to the Meng Residence...
...to deliver the final training manual to you.
Well...
My father is at home.
He won't let me meet with outsiders casually.
Then tomorrow...
...can you leave the residence tomorrow, Miss Meng?
Without a reason, why would Father let me leave the residence?
I should go.
If you're really that bored tonight,
wait for me at the back gate of the Meng Residence.
A Zi, are you tired?
Would you like to rest in the carriage?
I'm not tired.
Are you thirsty?
Would you like something to drink?
Seventh Cousin.
This entire journey,
you've asked Royal Sister countless times:
"Are you tired? Are you thirsty?"
Asking so many times,
aren't you tired or thirsty yourself?
Eldest Brother has been flipping through that love letter collection.
Why don't you ask if he's tired?
By the way, A Lan.
Give one copy of your love letter collection to Seventh Cousin.
I'll have the storyteller recite it at the Drunken Immortal Inn.
It's sure to attract many customers.
Are you sure?
Of course.
Even Eldest Brother likes it so much.
Alright.
Just don't regret it later.
Don't worry, I won't regret it.
In such a short time,
the plague in Jingzhou has already been controlled.
You truly have not disappointed Us.
We heard
you even contracted the plague in Jingzhou,
and nearly didn't wake up.
At that time, the plague was not yet eradicated.
This commoner dared not fail to wake up.
"Well, dared not fail to wake up."
Speak.
What reward do you desire?
This commoner has only one request.
I humbly beg Your Majesty to grant the Fifth Princess freedom in marriage.
Good.
We grant it.
When she returns to the palace,
We will inform her.
Could Your Majesty, for this commoner,
conceal the reason for going to Jingzhou?
Tomorrow, you shall begin your post at the Hanlin Academy.
If you have time,
you may enter the palace to spend more time with A Lan.
Your servant thanks Your Majesty.
What did you see?
To be so delighted?
Brother.
Look at A Lan.
You...
The grapes are quite good, aren't they?
I chose them personally.
Of course they're good.
I had the finest grapes prepared
all along the journey.
Yet I never heard her say a single word like,
"Are you thirsty?"
"Are you tired?"
How sarcastic.
Is this alright?
Brother.
Lord Yuwen and A Lan...
Let's go.
Opening the secret door to the forbidden area
will reveal the secrets within the Map of the Nine Provinces.
There is also a key in the Sword Maniac's possession.
Eldest Cousin and I have already sent people to search for it.
Prince Ning actually colluded with the Yunze Remnants.
You must uncover this person's identity.
Your child obeys the decree. Your servant obeys the decree.
The imperial physician says
Prince Ning has shown signs of waking recently.
After he awakens,
We will personally interrogate him.
Do you like it?
I do.
Princess.
Your servant and Xiao Li have prepared a gift for you too.
Really?
Let's go.
What is this?
It boosts your romantic luck.
It's quite effective, huh?
Princess, don't mind the details.
Xiao Li.
Bring the booklet.
Right away!
Princess, look.
And this is?
All the eligible bachelors in Luo Jing are listed here.
Your servant and Xi Xi ranked them by talent, family background,
character, and appearance.
The first place...
It's obvious.
...is Young Master Meng from the Meng Residence.
Young Master Meng just returned from Jingzhou yesterday.
His Majesty praised him for his merit in treating the plague.
He entered the Hanlin Academy directly.
Shao Jue agreed?
Of course!
Personally appointed by His Majesty.
What a great honor!
A young man who drinks and picks flowers.
Even drunk, his elegance is peerless.
Young Master Meng taking first place
is well-deserved.
Right.
Brother.
Are you alright?
I'm fine.
A Lan told me before
that she would absolutely not marry Yuwen Rui.
Yuwen Rui must have used some trick
during the southern trip.
That's why A Lan lost her senses.
Brother.
Next time I enter the palace,
I'll definitely talk some sense into her.
Make her see the error of her ways.
Turn back from the wrong path.
I have my own plans.
You don't need to worry too much.
About this matter...
Don't tell A Lan.
The more I draw, the uglier it gets.
The last one is just to fill the list.
That's Lord Yuwen.
Who told him to ask the Princess to cancel the engagement before?
Exactly.
There's something
I should mention.
What?
Your princess
already has an owner.
Who?
That blob.
What are you looking at?
Lord Yuwen! Lord Yuwen!
Who is this?
You may leave now.
Yes, yes.
A Lan is choosing a husband, I see.
How could that be?
I'm at the end.
You heard everything.
Why am I last?
You have high status.
You're the grand finale.
Back then, you told the Princess
to find a way to cancel the engagement herself.
Now you're
being inconsistent.
What's the real reason?
I know.
You must have seen Young Master Meng cares for the Princess,
and your pride acted up.
That's why you insincerely said you liked her.
Aren't all men like that?
We're both out here.
A man and a woman alone...
What if...
You go in and check.
No, you go.
You go.
What does 'high status' mean?
It means you're the most important.
The most important one
naturally appears last.
So can I understand it as...
I'm the most important in your heart?
Wishful thinking.
Then tell me,
who is the most important?
Why should I say it just because you told me to?
If you don't say it...
What then?
I'll...
I'm back.
Matron.
Stop running, Matron.
Don't run.
Come, come.
Come play with His Highness the Third Prince.
Matron.
Hurry up!
You should go back quickly. Wait.
Matron.
Let's play together.
Isn't the Third Prince already dead?
No, no.
His Highness the Third Prince is not dead.
Your Highness.
Your Highness is not afraid of fire.
The big fire is not scary.
Let's play, Matron.
Slow down, Matron. Be careful.
Don't fall.
What's wrong?
Do you remember
the situation after the Xicui Palace fire back then?
After the fire was extinguished,
the body of the Yunze prince was found.
It was already unrecognizable.
Melodramas are always like this.
Like falling off a cliff with no body found,
or a body burned beyond recognition...
Actually, they never died.
I have a feeling
the Third Prince of Yunze might still be alive.
Melodrama...
refers to those unoriginal storybooks.
You're really good at focusing on the key point.
I'll investigate this matter.
I'll come find you tonight.
I need to write a bit more.
If you're sleepy,
go rest first.
If the Princess isn't asleep,
how can this servant rest?
Right.
You're not worried Yuwen Rui will come for me, are you?
Wha... what is the Princess saying?
This servant doesn't know.
Don't know, don't know.
Fine.
Then I'm going to sleep.
If you're worried,
go guard the door.
The Princess is cunning.
Resourceful.
Very resourceful.
She's definitely not asleep yet.
Keep guarding.
To secretly meet Lord Yuwen,
the Princess actually climbed out the window.
Find her quickly!
Princess!
You little...
Still think you can keep your Princess in?
Who is A Lan waiting for?
Why are you here?
If I didn't come,
you wouldn't think to look for me.
The palace guards are truly useless.
Is everything alright for you in Jingzhou?
With you gone,
of course it's not good.
Can you be serious for once?
Is Yinglu doing alright?
I even brought her a gift.
She's doing great.
She's busy with more important matters now.
What are you looking at?
Nothing to see here.
Your outfit today
is just like
the green frog in the northeastern border swamps
that feeds on mosquitoes.
Now you're glaring,
looking even more like that green frog.
You... are quite cute.
Give it to me.
This booklet,
I started preparing it a long time ago.
Was the hundredth one difficult?
Not really.
You'll know when you see it.
What is this?
This is you, angry
when your purse was stolen.
This is me.
Well?
It looks quite like me, doesn't it?
Like.
Very much like.
My mother said I
had a talent for drawing since childhood.
Your mother must have doted on you.
This is you chasing me to give me a beating.
This is you practicing martial arts.
This is you holding your bottom and crying out in pain.
Why are you drawing me for no reason?
Look at the last page.
What nonsense did you write?
This is not nonsense.
I've wanted to write this for a long time.
I...
My heart belongs to you.
Miss Meng...
And you?
I...
I should go back first.
Me too.
So,
Yinglu and Commander He
have actually progressed to this point?
Commander He is quite something.
You prepared a gift for Yinglu.
What about mine?
Of course there's one for you too.
It's the same as Yinglu's.
I'll have someone fetch it.
The same as hers?
Then I don't want it.
I want...
just a hug.
Don't be so handsy all the time.
It's not proper.
Remember before you went to Luo Jing,
I told you
I had something to say to you.
What is it? Tell me.
You're being so mysterious.
First, have a drink with me.
Drink here?
The palace isn't a good place for drinking.
We should go outside the palace.
Consider it celebrating my entry into court service.
How about it?
Alright.
Let me change clothes then.
We'll go early and return early.
Yinglu told me
your reason for refusing to serve in court.
Although I don't know
why you've agreed to it now,
but as a friend,
I still hope you can
do what you love
and live freely and at ease.
Don't worry.
I will never do what I don't wish to do.
Taste this wine.
Crisp with a sweet aftertaste
It's truly excellent wine
I'm glad you like it
Jingzhou's fine wines are renowned everywhere
Among them, the Lover's Wine is the most famous
Lover's Wine
The name is quite lovely
It's brewed from the brightest flowers on the snowy mountain
and the snow from its highest peak
The local people regard the snowy mountain as a deity
If they have someone they love
they will circle the mountain forty-nine times
bowing and kowtowing with each step
praying to the deity to protect their beloved
keeping them safe from illness and misfortune for life
After completing the forty-nine circles
they go to the mountaintop to gather the flowers and snow
to brew a pot of Lover's Wine
How do you know all this so well?
In Jingzhou, I accidentally contracted the plague
I was bedridden for a long time
A commoner brewed a pot of Lover's Wine for me
You caught the plague too?
But thankfully, you're fine now
If I hadn't woken up
would A Lan have been sad?
Don't say such unlucky things
Wait
You just said
a commoner brewed Lover's Wine for you
That commoner was a woman, wasn't she?
The daughter of the Jingzhou Prefect
It seems the Prefect's daughter
has deep feelings for you
What we're drinking now is Lover's Wine
The one the Prefect's daughter brewed for you
I have no romantic feelings for her whatsoever
Naturally, I couldn't accept her wine
But what if this Lover's Wine
was brewed by me, personally for you?
A Lan, you're shocked
I'm teasing you
This isn't Jingzhou's Lover's Wine at all
It's just Luo Jing's Nuerhong wine
You really scared me
Your acting skills are wasted in this era
This Nuerhong is really quite good
Where did you buy it?
Yuwen Rui would definitely like it
I forgot
I'll tell you when I remember
You and Yuwen Rui...
That's a long story
Is there some happy occasion?
What did you need to see me about?
Regarding the death of the Third Prince of Yunze
I want you to investigate
He might still be alive
And also Matron Mo
have someone keep a close watch on her
Alright
After... after he tested the medicine for me
I... I realized
that I had actually liked him for a long time
So during your trip south
so much happened
Yes
If I had gone south with you back then
would everything be different?
The wine is delicious
Wait a moment
Yuwen Rui is looking for me
Right
Yuwen Rui
Regarding Matron Mo, I will...
You...
Look
Yuwen Rui, he...
will be here to find me soon